The shop will be open from 9.00 am this Saturday
商店将于这周六早上9点开业，
and if you go along to the opening then you'll have the chance to meet the national 400 metres running champion Paul King,
如果你去开幕式，你将会遇到国家400米跑步冠军保罗·金。
who's coming along to open the shop, and he will be staying around until about midday to chat to any fans who want to meet him and sign autographs.
他也将一起为商店开张，他将待到中午左右与粉丝聊天、签名。
Then there will be a whole range of special attractions all weekend.
然后在所有周末将会有大量吸引人的特殊项目。
There will be free tickets for local sporting events for the first 50 customers, and also a special competition open to all.
对于前50名的客人将会免费赠予当地体育赛事的门票，另外还有一个特殊的竞赛向公众开放。
Just answer fifteen out of twenty sports questions correctly to win a signed copy of Paul King's DVD 'Spring Tips',
只要从20道体育问题中回答正确15题，就能赢取保罗·金的签名光盘《Spring Tips》，
while the first person to get all the questions correct gets a year's free membership of the Bradcaster Gym.
第一位将所有问题回答正确的人将免费得到Bradcaster体育馆的全年会员资格。
All entrants will receive a special Sports calendar with details of all Bradcaster fixtures in the coming year.
所有参赛者都将获得一份特殊的体育日历，上面标有明年所有Bradcaster体育活动的详细信息。
One of the special opening offers is a fitness test - a complete review of your cardiac fitness and muscle tone,actually done in the shop by qualified staff.
其中一个特殊的开业特价是健康测试，由商店合格的工作人员全方面检查你的心脏健康和肌肉紧张度。
This would normally cost ￡30.00 but is available at half price for this month only.
这通常要花费30英镑，但是只在这个月半价。
There are only a limited number of places available for this,so to make a booking phone 560341.
这项活动的地方有限，所以要拨打560341进行电话预约。
In addition,if you open an account you get lots more special offers including the chance to try out equipment at special open evenings.
另外，如果你开一个账户，你会得到更多的特殊优惠，包括在特殊的开放日夜晚体验器材的机会。